/**
 * Created by David Snawder on 8/2/2016.
 */
var quiz1 = [{
    theQuestion: "How many pancakes do you think I can eat?",
    choices: ["All of them.", "Just one.", "Like a short stack or something.",
        "Trick question, they're waffles."],
    answer: 3
}, {
    theQuestion: "In the show Firefly, what is the name of the main ship?",
    choices: ["Firefly","Star Cruiser","Serenity","Trick question, it's a movie."],
    answer: 2
}, {
    theQuestion: "Books.",
    choices: ["Ehh.","Mmmm","CDs...What are we doing?","Ehh!"],
    answer: 3
}, {
    theQuestion: "Who was the original drummer for the band Toto?",
    choices: ["Mike Portnoy","Jeff Porcaro","Griffin Goldsmith","Me"],
    answer: 1
}
];

var quiz2 = [{
    theQuestion: "How many waffles do you think I can eat?",
    choices: ["All of them.", "Just one.", "Like two or three.",
        "Trick question, they're pancakes."],
    answer: 0
}, {
    theQuestion: "What is the movie companion to the show Firefly?",
    choices: ["Firefly: The Movie","Star Cruiser","Serenity","Trick question, there's no movie."],
    answer: 2
}, {
    theQuestion: "Games.",
    choices: ["Awww yeeee","Mmmmm","Books...What are we doing?","Yes"],
    answer: 0
}, {
    theQuestion: "Who was the second drummer for the band Toto?",
    choices: ["Mike Portnoy","Jeff Porcaro","Griffin Goldsmith","Simon something"],
    answer: 3
}
];

var quiz3 = [{
    theQuestion: "How many chicken tendies do you think I can eat?",
    choices: ["All of them.", "Just one.", "This joke isn't funny anymore.",
        "This joke wasn't funny to start with."],
    answer: 3
}, {
    theQuestion: "What is the book companion to the show Firefly?",
    choices: ["Firefly: The Movie","Star Cruiser","Serenity","Trick question, there's no book."],
    answer: 3
}, {
    theQuestion: "Films.",
    choices: ["Movies","Books","TV","Games"],
    answer: 0
}, {
    theQuestion: "Who is the drummer for the band Dawes?",
    choices: ["Mike Portnoy","Jeff Porcaro","Griffin Goldsmith","Simon something"],
    answer: 2
}
];